<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ProjectJU</string>
    <string name="title_activity_second">SecondActivity</string>

    <string name="iit">Institute of Information Technology establishes in 2009. Institute has goal to provide high end IT professionals.</string>

    <string name="Environmental_Science">The Department of Environmental Sciences is an academic department in the faculty of
        Mathematical and Physical Sciences of Jahangirnagar University. In addition to a full phase undergraduate program, the
        department also offers graduate degree programs leading to Master of Science (MS), Master of Philosophy (M.Phil) and Doctor
        of Philosophy (Ph.D) emphasizing basic research of a disciplinary of interdisciplinary nature. The unique juxtaposition of
        several sciences in one department fosters cooperation and exchange among traditional disciplines that share similar
        methodological and philosophical problems. The research endeavors of both faculty and graduate students, whether disciplinary or interdisciplinary, deal largely
        with problems of fundamental scientific interest and to a lesser extent with applied science, management or policy making.The Department of Environmental Sciences is an academic department in the faculty of
        Mathematical and Physical Sciences of Jahangirnagar University. In addition to a full phase undergraduate program, the
        department also offers graduate degree programs leading to Master of Science (MS), Master of Philosophy (M.Phil) and Doctor
        of Philosophy (Ph.D) emphasizing basic research of a disciplinary of interdisciplinary nature. The unique juxtaposition of
        several sciences in one department fosters cooperation and exchange among traditional disciplines that share similar
        methodological and philosophical problems. The research endeavors of both faculty and graduate students, whether disciplinary or interdisciplinary, deal largely
        with problems of fundamental scientific interest and to a lesser extent with applied science, management or policy making.</string>

    <string name="cse">The study of computer programming itself investigates various aspects of the use of programming languages
        and complex systems, and human-computer interaction
        focuses on the challenges in making computers and computations useful, usable, and universally accessible to humans.</string>

    <string name="statistics">The Department has more than 30 top-notched faculty members, well equipped and well-furnished computer
        lab, a seminar library, and a contemporary syllabus which is updated in every four years period. The department is a pioneer
        of having a computer lab. Because of lab facilities, all the students of the department are very proficient in statistical
        computing and using different statistical packages such as SPSS, STATA, Minitab, Eviews, and programming language including C++, FORTRAN, R, SAS, GAUSS,
        MATLAB etc. In addition, all the graduate students are capable enough to conduct research independently.</string>


</resources>
